addtext.com 2018-05-08

# AddText — Captions for your photos, quick and easy

## Privacy Notice

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for AddText.com which is run by FlamingText.com Pty Ltd. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site.

### Collection and Use of Information

**Personally identifiable information.** We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to and collect personally identifiable information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent any personally identifiable information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about new products or services, surveys or contests, or changes to this privacy policy.

**Non-personally identifiable information.** We collect non-personally identifiable information which is data that has not been directly associated to any specific individual. This includes keeping track of user activity as well as collecting the images that are created on our site. We may log information regarding user execution environments (eg. browser type, operating system, remote address). We also aggregate demographic information about users such as age, gender, location.

We use non-personally identifiable information to better understand our users so that we can improve our products, services and marketing strategies.

### Sharing of Information

We share aggregated demographic information with our advertisers to enable them to better target ad content to our users.

From time to time, you may be offered the opportunity to receive materials or special offers from third parties. If you opt-in to receive such information, we will with your permission share your name, email address and other information that you opt to provide to them.

We will not share your personally identifiable information with any third party outside of our organization other than as necessary to fulfill your request, to comply with the law or to satisfy any requirements in the event of a company reorganization that may involve the merger, acquisition or sale of our assets.

If you Share your creation, and allow "Public background", then this will allow others to use your image. You are agreeing to make it public. (If you don't agree, then de-select "Public background"). If you use our "Share" link, it will create a public facing page that anyone can view (if they know the URL). We don't currently link to the creations (Jan 2014), but in the future we may add a feature for people to view popular and recently created images. 

### Security

If we add user accounts or payment options, we will update this section to let you know what security precautions we take to protect your information.

### Third Party Advertisers

This site uses the services of Google, CasaleMedia, ValueClick, Tribal Fusion and other third parties to serve advertisements for promotions and other marketing messages when you visit our site. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to target advertisements for goods and services that are of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice, including your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit [Google](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/), [ValueClick](https://www.valueclickmedia.com/about/privacy), [Casale Media](https://casalemedia.com/privacy/). [Exponential (Tribal Fusion)](https://www.exponential.com/about-us/privacy.html). 

You can opt-out of most advertising at the [NAI Gateway](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

### Cookies

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Some services on this web site require that you are a registered user. To determine if you are registered and currently logged in, we use a cookie to keep track of this information. 

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy or if you have questions about this policy or suggestions on how to make it better, please[contact us](https://www.flamingtext.com/contactus/).**
